brightcherry.co.uk 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

### By using this website you give your consent that all personal data that you submit may be processed by BrightCherry in the manner and for the purposes described in the following Privacy Policy.

#### Definitions

The terms “Bright Cherry”, “BrightCherry Limited”, “BrightCherry”, “Bright Cherry Web Design”, “we”, “us”, “our” and “ours” when used in these Terms and Conditions mean BrightCherry Limited.

The terms “you”, “your” and “yours” when used in these Terms and Conditions mean any user of this website.

The term “Personal Data” refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, job title, email or mailing address.

#### About your privacy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors whilst providing the highest possible quality of service. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998.

If you have any questions concerning your personal information or regarding our practices, please contact: BrightCherry Limited, Allen House Business Centre, Unit P4, The Maltings, Station Road, Sawbridgeworth, Hertfordshire CM21 19X, telephone +44 (0)1279 729075 or send us an email.

#### Collection of personal data

We collect information from details you give us when you use our website or any of our services, and from any email messages you may send to us.

We may also collect email addresses via marketing events such as trade shows and exhibitions. In such cases, we assume that people providing their email addresses are opting in to receive email messages from us. Therefore, we do not include an email opt-out mechanism when collecting event leads.

If, at any time, you wish to opt out of receiving information from BrightCherry Limited via email, please telephone +44 (0)1279 729075 us or send us an email.

#### Anonymous data collected through this website

We also use software tools to collect information automatically about your visit to our website. The information obtained in this way, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form and, as such, cannot be used to identify you personally. Such aggregate information helps us to audit usage of our website and improve the service provided.

#### Cookies

In order to collect the anonymous data described above, we may use temporary “cookies” that collect the domain name of the user and the date and time you visited this website. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to discover the identity of the user. A cookie is a small piece of information which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and this enables you to decide if you want to accept it or not.

For more information on the cookies we store on your computer and how to disable them, please visit our Cookies policy page.

#### Use of personal data

We process your personal data only for specific and limited purposes. We ask only for data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes. When we ask you for personal data, we tell you the purposes for which we will process that data. Some of these purposes include:

  * Providing you with information about our products or services, special offers and events or articles and case studies we think will be of interest to you
  * Sending you regular newsletters by email or by post
  * Providing you with product or service information and promotional material that you have specifically requested
  * Processing any other requests that you make
  * To summarise usage behaviour for advertisers and partners, and to describe our service and performance. This is not based on individual behaviour, but is generic
  * Conducting marketing research.

#### Disclosure of your personal data

We do not share, sell or distribute your personal data with unrelated third parties, except under the following limited circumstances:

  * Personal data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for or on behalf of BrightCherry Limited, or in connection with the business of BrightCherry Limited for further processing in accordance with the purposes to which you have subsequently consented.
  * We may share or transfer the information in our databases to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interest, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this website, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganisation, dissolution or similar event.

#### Data integrity and security

We keep your personal data only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or to comply with any applicable legal or ethical reporting or document retention requirements.

In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our servers and our databases are protected by industry standard security technology, such as industry standard firewalls and password protection.

The employees who have access to personal data have been trained to handle such data properly and in accordance with our security protocols and strict standards of confidentiality. Although we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorised disclosure, alteration or destruction of data, we try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

#### Data access and corrections

We will disclose to you the personal data we hold about you upon receipt of your written request addressed to the address given above. We will also correct, amend or delete any personal data that is inaccurate and notify any third party recipients of the necessary changes.

#### Links to other websites

This Privacy Policy applies only to www.brightcherry.co.uk. These websites contain hyperlinks to websites that are not operated by BrightCherry Limited. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and you should note that we do not have any control over these other websites. We cannot, therefore, be responsible for the protection and privacy of any data which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and review the privacy statement posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal data about yourself.

#### Updates and changes to privacy policy

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on this website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site.

#### Governing law

This Privacy Policy forms part of our website Terms and Conditions and as such shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England. You agree to submit any dispute arising out of your use of this website to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England.
